<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Eternal Engine</title>
    <link>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Eternal Engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.134.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>/r/WorldNews Live Thread: Russian Invasion of Ukraine Day 1142, Part 1 (Thread #1289)</title>
      <link>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/2025-04-11-rworldnews-live-thread-russ/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/2025-04-11-rworldnews-live-thread-russ/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Russian Invasion of Ukraine: A Ongoing Crisis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the world continues to monitor the situation in Ukraine, the latest development in the ongoing crisis has unfolded. The Russian invasion of Ukraine, which began on February 24th, marks day 1142 since the conflict started. In this live thread, Redditors are coming together to share news, updates, and analysis on the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Developments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to reports, Ukrainian forces have made significant gains in the Donbas region, pushing Russian troops back in several areas. The developments come as a response to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s counteroffensive efforts aimed at retaking control of occupied territories. Meanwhile, Russia continues to claim that its military operations are focused on &amp;ldquo;denazifying&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;demilitarizing&amp;rdquo; Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global News Update</title>
      <link>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/2025-04-10-global-news-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/2025-04-10-global-news-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Title: Global News Update: A Comprehensive Roundup of World Events&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving landscape of our world, it is essential to stay informed about the latest global news updates. This brief roundup aims to bring you a compact yet comprehensive summary of significant events happening around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Climate Change: The United Nations (UN) COP26 summit concluded in Glasgow, Scotland, with 197 countries agreeing on steps to combat climate change. Notable commitments include phasing out coal and reducing methane emissions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP Pauses Reciprocal Tariffs for 90 Days for Everyone but China</title>
      <link>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://Davis345678.github.io/eternal-engine-site/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recent decision by TRUMP to pause reciprocal tariffs&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-body&#34;&gt;Main Body&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This move aims to ease tensions with global trade partners&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In summary, this tariff pause could reshape international trade dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
